

## CONTACT

Kigali, Rwanda 00000

+250792390788

ghislainhirwa11@gmail.

### SKILLS

- Software Production
- Robotics
- · Project Management
- Advertisement production
- Special effects and restoration
- 3D project illustration

### CERTIFICATIONS

- Certified UI/UX Designer
- Chartered full-stack developer

LANGUAGES	
English: First Language	
English:	C1
Advanced	
French:	В2
Upper Intermediate	
Kinyarwanda:	C2

Proficient

## **Ghislain Hirwa**

Expert Graphic designer and motion-video editing expert with skills in requirements definition, unique and creativity generation and team collaboration. Innovative and creative in developing fresh designs to meet current and forecasted needs. Works great with technical and non-technical teams to coordinate on-time, quality releases.

#### EXPERIENCE

35/2024 - 08/2024

0/2023 - 01/2024

M/2023 - 07/2023

## 3D Graphic Designer

Mashirika Performing Arts And Media Company - Kigali

Creating a virtual art gallery displaying their work of all years
 Depicted objects in motion in 2D and 3D designs using blender and unity.

## Trainee Software Engineer

Klab-Fablab - Kigali, Rwanda

 Used extensive practical and theoretical understanding of various coding languages to aid software development.

Offered adaptive coding support, using working knowledge of Javascript, Python and SQL.

 Applied software engineering best practices with a security-first mindset.

Helped senior engineers convert operational needs into technical requirement specifications.

Contributed to design of high-level software architectures.

#### Intern

Ishyiga Foundation - Kigali, Rwanda

Designed and maintained network traffic monitoring system to support network administrators.

Improved development timeline by implementing test case plans based on real-world case scenarios.

Installed new software systems, collaborating with UX team to design and implement new features.

Conducted end-to-end unit testing and post-production testing, collaborating with quality assurance testers.

#### EDUCATION

2022 - Current

# A-Levels Software development and embedded system Rwanda Coding Academy - Nyabihu

- Member of the red-cross community
- · President of the Music club
- Health prefect